{
    "subject": "resource/Jos\u00e9_Domingues_dos_Santos",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/description",
    "object": "Portuguese prime-minister",
    "human_readable": "Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos' description is Portuguese prime-minister.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9806946516036987,
            "question": "Which country's prime minister is Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9227997660636902,
            "question": "What is the description of Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8836666941642761,
            "question": "Who is Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.809664249420166,
            "question": "What is the significance of Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos in Portuguese politics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8072537779808044,
            "question": "What nationality is Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7922344207763672,
            "question": "What is Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos' profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7459505200386047,
            "question": "Is Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos a political figure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7117312550544739,
            "question": "Where might we find more information about Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6702501177787781,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos' role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6142615079879761,
            "question": "What position does Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos hold?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos' description is Portuguese prime-minister.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2054_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos' role?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2054_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might we find more information about Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2054_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos a political figure?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2054_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2054_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2054_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2054_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2054_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2054_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2054_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2054_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2054_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2054_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2054_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the documents, Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos has served as a member of the National Parliament and as a Minister of Agriculture, but there is no mention of him holding the office of Portuguese prime-minister."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided context does not mention Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos having been a Prime Minister of Portugal. According to the information given, he served as a member of the National Parliament and was appointed as Minister of Agriculture in 2009 under the government of Prime Minister Pedro Passos Coelho. There is no indication that he ever held the position of Prime Minister himself."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos was a member of the Portuguese National Parliament and served as Minister of Agriculture, but he was not the Prime Minister of Portugal.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There are two distinct individuals mentioned in the context information - Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos from Portugal and another individual (name not specified) who served as Angola's prime minister. The descriptions of their careers, roles, and actions suggest that they are two different people with different nationalities and affiliations.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos served as Minister of Agriculture in Portugal but there is no information suggesting he was the Portuguese Prime Minister.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}